nettyfish.com 2018-12-03

# Privacy Policy

##  [ Privacy Policy](http://nettyfish.com/index.php/privacy-policy)

     Category: [Uncategorised](http://nettyfish.com/index.php/privacy-policy/2-uncategorised)
     Published: Tuesday, 19 December 2017 11:53 
     Written by Super User 
     Hits: 3433 

PRIVACY POLICY

**Nettyfish Networks Private Limited** and its affiliated Companies (Collectively known as “NFN PVT. LTD.”) is sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet. We believe it is important to you to know how we treat the information we receive from you, while visiting NFN PVT. LTD. websites. This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personal Information’ (“PI”) is being used online. PI, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personal Information in accordance with our website.

  * **1\. What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website, blog or app?**

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number, Company Name, Country, queries or other details to help you with your experience.

While sharing personal information, you recognize and understand that there is no compulsion on you to provide us with your personal information and any and all personal information provided by you to us is with your full consent, own volition and desire to provide such personal information. You also understand that we are under no obligation to verify the source from which the personal information about you is provided to us, and they are deemed to be provided by you, unless you demonstrate to us within a period of fifteen days from the date of providing of such information to us, to our satisfaction, that the information was provided to us without your free consent.

  * **2\. When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you fill out a form or enter information on our website.

  * **3\. How do we use your information?**

We may use the information:

  * i) To follow up after correspondence (email or phone inquiries);
  * ii) To understand your requirements;
  * iii) To send you promotional emails;
  * iv) To research and update the services as per your requirement;
  * v) To serve you better.
  * **4\. How do we protect your information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We secure your personal information through regular malware scanning.

Your personal information is secured behind networks which is accessible to a limited Company Personnel who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

Also, all transactions are processed through a gateway provider which are not stored or processed on our servers.

  * **5\. Do we use'cookies'?**

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we may use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We may also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We may use cookies to:

  * • Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If users disable cookies in their browser:

some features will be disabled. Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

  * **6\. Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personal Information.

  * **7\. Third-party links**

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

  * **8\. Other Websites Link**

NFN PVT. LTD. Web site may contain links to other sites such as NFN PVT. LTD. partners and affiliates. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.

  * **9\. Refund and cancellation Policy**

#### No  refund and cancellation  Policy

Please read this policy carefully. This is the Return and Refund Policy of Nettyfish.

No Refund: All services are sold "as it is". You assume the responsibility for your purchase, and no refunds will be issued. we do not issue refund for digital or online services.

Once the services are purchased, there is no option to cancel the service

You can contact us for assistance  if you experience any issues when using our services.

No Exchange: There is no exchange of services.

**CONTACTING US**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the Contact us page available on the website.
